[DOOR CLOSES]
ALL:
Ah.
(Howard:)Hey, you know
what would be a great idea?
(Howard:)We get some girls over here
and play Laser Obstacle Strip Chess.
Believe me, any girl willing to play that,
you don't wanna see naked.
(Howard:)You underestimate me.
(Sheldon:)Penny.
Penny. Penny.
(Penny:)Hey, Sheldon.
- It's 11 a.m.
- I know. You're safe.
(Sheldon:)This package came
while you were at work.
(Penny:)Great, my rhinestones. Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- What?
(Sheldon:)You have to sign this.
(Penny:)What is it?
(Sheldon:)When I signed for the package, I was
deputized by the United Parcel Service...
(Sheldon:)...and entrusted with its final delivery.
I need you to acknowledge receipt...
(Sheldon:)...so that I'm fully indemnified
and no longer liable.